我们，是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
♪ and if you think we can't, ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ we'll always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文！
and Steven!
到此为止
翻译
草
校对
右翼部鸣明/presisco
特效
CCCC
压制
DDDD
是他们吗？
These the ones?
史蒂文！格雷格！
\Steven! Greg!
他们揭穿我了！
They found me out!
紫晶！
Amethyst!
你根本无法想象我经历了什么
You won't believewhat I've been through.
这些紫晶们，他们真的，真的…
These Amethysts,they're really, really...
…棒极了！
great!
蛤？！
What?!
瞧你那张脸！
Your faces!
你说对了！这太好笑啦！
You were right!That was priceless!
抱歉，抱歉！不这么做不行啊！
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!I had to!
你穿的什么玩意儿？
What are you wearing?
格雷格！你这身真不错
Greg! This isa good look for you.
都发生了些什么？
What is going on?
这些紫晶都来自地球！
These Amethysts,they're all from Earth!
他们都来自主宝宝基地！
They're from the Prime Kindergarten!
等等！嘿，8XL！
Wait! Hey, 8XL!
怎么了？
Yeah?
伙计们，我也来自8号区！
You guys, I'm an 8!
快告诉他们. 快告诉他们！
Tell them. Tell them!
在我后面孵化的紫晶一直都没有出土
The amethyst under menever popped out.
我们等了好久但…噗——什么都没发生
We were all waiting,and -- pfft -- nothing.
我是8XM！刻面5，切面8XM——这是我！
I'm 8XM!Facet 5, cut 8XM -- that's me!
这是8XG，这是8XH
This is 8XG,this is 8XH.
我是J
I'm J.-
啊，臭记性！抱歉！我比霍利蓝玛瑙还健忘！
Sorry!I'm worse than Holly Blue!
我们不都有点吗？
Aren't we all?
主基地，主基地，主基地
Prime, prime, prime.
你们这群紫晶真排外
You Amethysts areso cliquey.
这个瘦子是个铁石英！
Skinny's a Jasper!
这里也有来自副宝宝基地的宝石！
There are Gems herefrom the Beta Kindergarten, too!
嘿，红玉髓跑哪去了？
Hey, where's Carnelian?
正在庆祝呢
Celebrating.
我再也不是最矮的那个咯！
I'm not the shortest anymore!
这太不真实了
This is unreal.
嘿！
Hey!
拜托了，如果你们不介意我想问
Please, if you don't mind me asking,
我们真的需要你们的帮助
we really needyour help.
我们和蓝宝石，红宝石，还有珍珠走失了
We came inwith Sapphire, Ruby, and Pearl,
我们必须要找到他们，然后离开——
we've got to find themand get out of --
请稍等片刻
I'll only be a moment.
你们在这儿干嘛呢？！
What are you alldoing in here?!
快去你们各自的岗位站好！
Get to your stations!
包括你们两个丑陋掉色的副基地来的！
Even you hideousoff-color betas!
滚出你们的鸽棚，赶快回到岗位上！
Get out of your cubbiesand into your places!
这是你们唯一能报答钻石们的大恩大德的机会
It's the least you can dofor the Diamond
让你们这群没用的可悲的宝石有用武之地
that kept your worthless,sorry Gems in service!
没错——蓝钻马上就要回来了！
That's right --Blue is back already!
现在马上让我瞧瞧你们肮脏的石英血脉
Now go pretend your filthy vein of Quartz
还能做些什么值得尊敬的事！
is capable of gratitude!
快去，快去，快去！
Go, go, go!
解散！我的钻石还在等着呢！
Disperse! My Diamond is waiting!
跑！赶快跑！
Run! Just run!
我会找到你们的！快跑！
I'll find you! Go!
是谁用泡泡封起了这些宝石？
Who bubbledall these Gems?
哇哦！
Wow!
这里就像个生日派对
It's kind of like a birthday party in here.
哦不！
Oh, no!
我们得藏起来！
We got to hide!
珍珠，关门
Pearl,close the door.
求你告诉我你在开玩笑
Please tell me you're joking.
你刚离开这里，就又回来了？
You only just left,and you're already back?
黄钻！你-你在这里做什么？
Yellow!W-What are you doing here?
我来带你回到现实世界，蓝
I'm here to bring youback to reality, Blue.
我不需要
I'm fine.
请让我独自待会
Just leave me alone.
已经过去几千年了，蓝
It's beenthousands of years, Blue,
可你依旧无法下手摧毁这些宝石？
and you still can't bringyourself to destroy these Gems?
她是被一颗玫瑰石英粉碎的！
She was shatteredby a Rose Quartz!
所有玫瑰石都该接受同样的命运！
The entire cut of Gemdeserves the same fate!
但她们是…她的
But they were hers.
她们应该从这世上彻底被销毁
They should bewiped out of existence,
而不是安逸地躺在泡泡中！
not kept safe in bubbles!
黄，她创造了她们
Yellow,she made them.
这是我们仅有的…她的遗产——
This is allwe have left of her --
这些宝石，这个宫殿，和地球
these Gems, this place,and the Earth.
我想我们应该已经达成共识了
I thought we agreedwe need to put that planet
我们要忘却那颗星球，走出这座废墟
and this whole debaclebehind us.
你为什么就不能让我独自哀悼呢？
Why can't you justlet me grieve?
你不能永远停留在这里！
You can't keepcoming here forever!
为什么不能？
Why not?
珍珠，做些什么
Pearl, do something.
唱首歌，安慰一下她
Sing for her.Make her feel better.
好的，我的钻石！
Yes, my Diamond!
咳咳
Ahem.
咳咳！
Ahem!
呃…哦
Uh...oh.
啊～哈哈，啊～哈哈
♪ Aah haa haa, aah haa haa ♪
啊～哈哈～哈哈～哈哈
♪ Aah haa haa haa haa haa haa ♪
啊～哈哈，啊～哈哈
♪ Aah haa haa, aah haa haa ♪
啊～哈哈～哈哈～哈哈～哈～哈～～
♪ Aah haa haa haa haa haa haa haa haaaaaa ♪
你为何要在此停留？
♪ Why would you want to be here? ♪
在这能看到什么？
♪ What do you ever see here?
这岂不让你更加悲伤？
♪ That doesn't make you feel worse than you do? ♪
请说，情感用处是何，蓝？
♪ And tell me, what's the use of feeling, Blue? ♪
为何你想雇佣那些
♪ Why would you want to employ her♪
毁灭她的遗物？
♪ subjects that destroyed her?
何苦维护动物园？
♪ Why keep up her silly zoo?
哦，请说
♪ Oh, tell me
情感用处是何，蓝？
♪ What's the use of feeling, Blue? ♪
军队有用处，能进行一场战争
♪ An army has a use, they can go and fight a war ♪
蓝宝石有用处，她可以见时知己
♪ A Sapphire has a use, she can tell you what it's for ♪
蓝玛瑙能慑人，青金石能塑星
♪ An Agate terrifies, a Lapis tear a port ♪
当她们需要钻石时你在哪，蓝？
♪ Where's their Diamond when they need her, Blue? ♪
你必须要挺起胸来，蓝
♪ You've got to be a leader, Blue ♪
对，当然，我们还爱她
♪ Yes, of course, we still love her ♪
而且永不会忘记她
♪ And we're always thinking of her ♪
但空是怀念没有用
♪ But now there's nothing we can do ♪
那请说
♪ So tell me
情感用处是何？
♪ What's the use of feeling? ♪
情感用处是何，蓝？
♪ What's the use of feeling, Blue? ♪
哦
♪ Ohh
你怎能做到面对这里
♪ How can you stand to be here with it all? ♪
面对这里
♪ Here with it all
被自己的悔恨淹没？
♪ Drowning in all this regret?
忘记她不是更好吗？
♪ Wouldn't you rather forget her? ♪
哦～哦
♪ Ohhh
难道不更应抛下过去？
♪ Won't it be grand to get rid of it all? ♪
抛下过去
♪ Rid of it all
让我们准备进攻
♪ Let's make a plan of attack
停止回首然后展望未来
♪ Start looking forward and stop looking back ♪
哦
♪ Oh
对，当然，我们还爱着她
♪ yes, of course, we still love her
而且永不会忘记她
♪ And we're always thinking of her ♪
我其实也在想着她
♪ Don't you know I miss her, too? ♪
但请说
♪ But tell me
感情用处是何？
♪ What's the use of feeling? ♪
嗯～哼哼，嗯～哼哼
♪ Hmm hmm hmm, hmm hmm hmm
嗯～哼哼～哼哼～哼哼～哼～哼～～
♪ Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmmmmm ♪
我们到了
And we have arrived.
退下吧，珍珠
That will be all, Pearl.
我的钻石
My Diamond.
我高贵的优雅的不可思议光辉夺目的钻石…
My gracious, wondrous,luminous, lustrous Diamond.
…们？
Sss?
哦，我的天！
Oh, my!
这真是我莫大的荣耀，能沐浴您们的光辉…们
It's truly an honorto bask in your radiance...ses.
讲重点，玛瑙
Get to the point,Agate.
是的，当然，对此致以我最诚挚的歉意
Yes, of course.My deepest apologies.
您一定很乐意得知您的蓝宝石
You'll be pleased to knowthat your Sapphire
已经将您的货物安全送达
has completedyour special delivery.
什么货物？
What special delivery?
呃，那个特殊的
Um, the special delivery
您要求的来自地球的货物，当然
you requested from Earth,of course.
我从未要求过任何蓝宝石去地球
I never asked any Sapphire to go to Earth.
我…
I...
呃…
Um...
哦不！她开始结冰了！
Oh, no!She's freezing up!
我的…预知能力看到了您，我的钻石
My...future vision foresaw you,my Diamond,
会希望有更多…人类来到这个动物园
desiring more...humans for the zoo.
所以我…就擅自行事了
So I...acted accordingly.
这是真的
It's true.
保留地球标本的区域要关闭了
The window for preserving Earth specimens is closing.
咻
Phew!
这就是你想要的？
Is that what you want?
蓝宝石，融合体开始孵化了吗？
Sapphire, has the clusteremerged yet?
不，它还没有
No, it has not.
那么我们还有时间
Then there's still time.
就这样吧
That will be all.
我的钻石们
My Diamonds.
两颗钻石？！
Two Diamonds?!
我不敢相信！你能相信吗？
I can't believe it!Can you believe it?
哦，这个，你当然可以相信
Oh, well,of course you can.
你估计已经预见到一切了
You probably foresaw the whole thing.
当然！一点都不惊讶
Of course!No surprises here.
我从未想过能亲眼见到黄钻
I never expected to seeYellow Diamond in person.
多么威严啊
What a commanding presence.
你能在她身上直接感受到
You can just feelstrength and confidence
那份力量和自信
radiating from her.
不要误会我，当然了
Don't misunderstand me,of course.
我永远都会衷心于蓝钻
I'll always bein Blue's confidence,
但如果我生来为黄钻效力
but if I had been made for Yellow,
我也不会有怨言的
you wouldn't see me complaining.
我希望她们会欣赏我
I do hope they appreciate all my hard work
辛苦保留下的粉钻的遗产
to preserve the Pink Diamond legacy.
这样我被分配到这里
It would really make it worth being stationed here
指挥这些可怜的宝石们也值了
with these sorry excuses for Gems.
哦！当然，太可惜了
Ohhh!It's a shame, though.
这个哨位太偏远了
This out post is so remote.
我甚至开始觉得我们被遗忘了
I was beginning to think we'd been forgotten.
但我们还没有！
But we haven't!
见到两颗钻石——在一天内！
Two Diamonds -- one day!
多大的荣誉啊
What an honor.
没什么能搅乱我心情了
I don't think anythingcould spoil this for me.
这…是……
What...is...
什么意思？！
the meaning of this?!
这两只怎么逃离控制区域了？！
Why are these twooutside the containment area?!
霍利蓝玛瑙，我可以解释
Holly Blue, I can explain.
不需要了，您的明晰
No need, your Clarity.
可能您都无法预料到
Not even you could have foreseen
这些紫晶有多不可靠！
how incompetent these Amethysts are.
当然，如果想让一切走上正路
Well, if you want something done right,
你只能亲自动手
you just do it yourself.
你们两个跟我走！
You two are coming with me!
石榴！
Garnet!
史蒂文，带格雷格上船！
Steven,get Greg on board!
好的，拜托了！
Yes, please!
交给我们吧
We'll handle this noise.
哦哦哦！
Ooooooh!
这一天我等了好久了
I've been waiting to do this all day.
呃！
Unh!
你们在干什么呢？！她们是叛徒！
What are you doing?!They're traitors!
毁掉她们！
Destroy them!
再见！再见！再见！
Bye!Bye!        Bye!- Bye!
一生荣誉，紫晶
Famethyst for life!
我会向钻石通报你们的！
I'll report youto the Diamonds!
你们全部！全部都会被粉碎！
All of you!You'll all be shattered!
你真的打算告诉钻石们
You're really gonna tell the Diamonds
你允许了一群叛徒
that you allowed a band of traitorous rebels
大摇大摆进入了一个戒备森严的机构
to infiltrate a highly secure facility
然后在你眼皮底下溜走了？
and escape from right under your careful watch?
听上去不像什么明智之举哦，霍利
Doesn't sound like a wise thing to do, Holly Blue.
所以为了你自己，管好你的嘴巴
So do yourself a favorand keep your mouth shut.
就这样吧
That will be all.
太谢谢你们来救我了
Thanks so muchfor coming to get me.
这算是我人生中第三疯狂的周末了
That has to be likethe third-craziest weekend I've ever had.
爸爸，对不起，我让你卷入了这一切
Dad, I'm really sorryI got you into all this.
这一切都只是因为我的好奇心
This whole thing started cause I wanted answers.
你不需要为任何事感到抱歉
You don't have to be sorry about a thing.
我希望你找到了你想要的
I hope you found what you were looking for.
我找到了
I did.
我找到了你
I found you.